{"RT_log_version":"1.0.1","RT_log_data":[{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.mn:0..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF1-BL4.incr.1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549087692024","data":{"timestamp":" 1549087692024"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190202_090802"," gameId":" 5c1af455-ea1c-413f-83b5-265dd70e2cba"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.mn_0..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF1-BL4.incr.1"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_10_2-10-11"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 10"," userResponse":" 10"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.mn:0..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF1-BL4.incr.1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549087696388","data":{"timestamp":" 1549087696388"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190202_090802"," gameId":" 5c1af455-ea1c-413f-83b5-265dd70e2cba"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.mn_0..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF1-BL4.incr.1"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_12_12-5-6"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 12"," userResponse":" 12"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.mn:0..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF1-BL4.incr.1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549087701438","data":{"timestamp":" 1549087701438"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190202_090802"," gameId":" 5c1af455-ea1c-413f-83b5-265dd70e2cba"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.mn_0..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF1-BL4.incr.1"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_9_0-9-7"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 9"," userResponse":" 9"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.mn:0..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF1-BL4.incr.1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549087706415","data":{"timestamp":" 1549087706415"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190202_090802"," gameId":" 5c1af455-ea1c-413f-83b5-265dd70e2cba"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.mn_0..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF1-BL4.incr.1"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_12_13-12-5"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 12"," userResponse":" 12"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.mn:0..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF1-BL4.incr.1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549087712057","data":{"timestamp":" 1549087712057"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190202_090802"," gameId":" 5c1af455-ea1c-413f-83b5-265dd70e2cba"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.mn_0..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF1-BL4.incr.1"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_11_10-11-12"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 11"," userResponse":" 11"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.mn:0..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF1-BL4.incr.1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549087717062","data":{"timestamp":" 1549087717062"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190202_090802"," gameId":" 5c1af455-ea1c-413f-83b5-265dd70e2cba"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.mn_0..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF1-BL4.incr.1"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_7_10-3-7"," problemNumber":" 6"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 7"," userResponse":" 10"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.mn:0..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF1-BL4.incr.1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549087723173","data":{"timestamp":" 1549087723173"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190202_090802"," gameId":" 5c1af455-ea1c-413f-83b5-265dd70e2cba"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.mn_0..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF1-BL4.incr.1"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_7_10-3-7"," problemNumber":" 6"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 7"," userResponse":" 3"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.mn:0..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF1-BL4.incr.1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549087728932","data":{"timestamp":" 1549087728932"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190202_090802"," gameId":" 5c1af455-ea1c-413f-83b5-265dd70e2cba"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.mn_0..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF1-BL4.incr.1"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_7_10-3-7"," problemNumber":" 6"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 7"," userResponse":" 7"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.mn:0..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF1-BL4.incr.1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549087735541","data":{"timestamp":" 1549087735541"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190202_090802"," gameId":" 5c1af455-ea1c-413f-83b5-265dd70e2cba"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.mn_0..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF1-BL4.incr.1"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_10_3-10-2"," problemNumber":" 7"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 10"," userResponse":" 2"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.mn:0..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF1-BL4.incr.1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549087741789","data":{"timestamp":" 1549087741789"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190202_090802"," gameId":" 5c1af455-ea1c-413f-83b5-265dd70e2cba"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.mn_0..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF1-BL4.incr.1"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_10_3-10-2"," problemNumber":" 7"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 10"," userResponse":" 10"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.mn:0..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF1-BL4.incr.1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549087750678","data":{"timestamp":" 1549087750678"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190202_090802"," gameId":" 5c1af455-ea1c-413f-83b5-265dd70e2cba"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.mn_0..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF1-BL4.incr.1"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_10_1-10-6"," problemNumber":" 8"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 10"," userResponse":" 10"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.mn:0..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF1-BL4.incr.1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549087755652","data":{"timestamp":" 1549087755652"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190202_090802"," gameId":" 5c1af455-ea1c-413f-83b5-265dd70e2cba"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.mn_0..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF1-BL4.incr.1"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_4_0-4-13"," problemNumber":" 9"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 4"," userResponse":" 4"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.mn:0..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF1-BL4.incr.1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549087761113","data":{"timestamp":" 1549087761113"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190202_090802"," gameId":" 5c1af455-ea1c-413f-83b5-265dd70e2cba"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.mn_0..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF1-BL4.incr.1"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_3_3-13-6"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 3"," userResponse":" 3"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.mn:0..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF1-BL4.incr.1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549087767690","data":{"timestamp":" 1549087767689"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190202_090802"," gameId":" 5c1af455-ea1c-413f-83b5-265dd70e2cba"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.mn_0..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF1-BL4.incr.1"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" BPOP_3_3-13-6"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:2ch..2ch.syl.rand.sim.stat.show.48__it_7","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549087776589","data":{"timestamp":" 1549087776589"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190202_090802"," gameId":" bded9204-eea0-43db-bcfc-33def099b290"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_2ch..2ch.syl.rand.sim.stat.show.48__it_7"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_ri_ri-fi-si"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" ri"," userResponse":" ri"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:2ch..2ch.syl.rand.sim.stat.show.48__it_7","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549087780843","data":{"timestamp":" 1549087780843"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190202_090802"," gameId":" bded9204-eea0-43db-bcfc-33def099b290"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_2ch..2ch.syl.rand.sim.stat.show.48__it_7"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_go_go-lo-po"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" go"," userResponse":" go"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:2ch..2ch.syl.rand.sim.stat.show.48__it_7","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549087785317","data":{"timestamp":" 1549087785317"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190202_090802"," gameId":" bded9204-eea0-43db-bcfc-33def099b290"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_2ch..2ch.syl.rand.sim.stat.show.48__it_7"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_me_le-me-re"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" me"," userResponse":" me"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:2ch..2ch.syl.rand.sim.stat.show.48__it_7","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549087789450","data":{"timestamp":" 1549087789450"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190202_090802"," gameId":" bded9204-eea0-43db-bcfc-33def099b290"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_2ch..2ch.syl.rand.sim.stat.show.48__it_7"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_vo_vo-po-to"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" vo"," userResponse":" vo"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:2ch..2ch.syl.rand.sim.stat.show.48__it_7","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549087794284","data":{"timestamp":" 1549087794284"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190202_090802"," gameId":" bded9204-eea0-43db-bcfc-33def099b290"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_2ch..2ch.syl.rand.sim.stat.show.48__it_7"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_po_po-to-vo"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" po"," userResponse":" po"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:2ch..2ch.syl.rand.sim.stat.show.48__it_7","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549087799479","data":{"timestamp":" 1549087799479"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190202_090802"," gameId":" bded9204-eea0-43db-bcfc-33def099b290"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_2ch..2ch.syl.rand.sim.stat.show.48__it_7"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_bu_bu-zu-fu"," problemNumber":" 6"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" bu"," userResponse":" bu"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:2ch..2ch.syl.rand.sim.stat.show.48__it_7","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549087805096","data":{"timestamp":" 1549087805096"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190202_090802"," gameId":" bded9204-eea0-43db-bcfc-33def099b290"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_2ch..2ch.syl.rand.sim.stat.show.48__it_7"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_fa_fa-ra-sa"," problemNumber":" 7"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" fa"," userResponse":" fa"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:2ch..2ch.syl.rand.sim.stat.show.48__it_7","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549087809999","data":{"timestamp":" 1549087809999"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190202_090802"," gameId":" bded9204-eea0-43db-bcfc-33def099b290"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_2ch..2ch.syl.rand.sim.stat.show.48__it_7"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_mo_mo-ko-ro"," problemNumber":" 8"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" mo"," userResponse":" mo"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:2ch..2ch.syl.rand.sim.stat.show.48__it_7","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549087815239","data":{"timestamp":" 1549087815239"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190202_090802"," gameId":" bded9204-eea0-43db-bcfc-33def099b290"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_2ch..2ch.syl.rand.sim.stat.show.48__it_7"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_li_li-ji-si"," problemNumber":" 9"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" li"," userResponse":" li"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:2ch..2ch.syl.rand.sim.stat.show.48__it_7","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549087846194","data":{"timestamp":" 1549087846194"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190202_090802"," gameId":" bded9204-eea0-43db-bcfc-33def099b290"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_2ch..2ch.syl.rand.sim.stat.show.48__it_7"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_pu_pu-ru-lu"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" pu"," userResponse":" pu"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:2ch..2ch.syl.rand.sim.stat.show.48__it_7","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549087851978","data":{"timestamp":" 1549087851977"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190202_090802"," gameId":" bded9204-eea0-43db-bcfc-33def099b290"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_2ch..2ch.syl.rand.sim.stat.show.48__it_7"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" BPOP_pu_pu-ru-lu"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549087861273","data":{"timestamp":" 1549087861272"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190202_090802"," gameId":" 85218cb8-aca4-4daa-b15d-aa44a66d5f35"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mbuga za wanyama Tanzania"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MBUGA"," userResponse":" MBUGA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549087861502","data":{"timestamp":" 1549087861501"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190202_090802"," gameId":" 85218cb8-aca4-4daa-b15d-aa44a66d5f35"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mbuga za wanyama Tanzania"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ZA"," userResponse":" ZA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549087862474","data":{"timestamp":" 1549087862473"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190202_090802"," gameId":" 85218cb8-aca4-4daa-b15d-aa44a66d5f35"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mbuga za wanyama Tanzania"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WANYAMA"," userResponse":" WANYAMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549087863757","data":{"timestamp":" 1549087863756"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190202_090802"," gameId":" 85218cb8-aca4-4daa-b15d-aa44a66d5f35"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mbuga za wanyama Tanzania"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TANZANIA"," userResponse":" TANZANIA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549087866692","data":{"timestamp":" 1549087866691"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190202_090802"," gameId":" 85218cb8-aca4-4daa-b15d-aa44a66d5f35"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ya kwanza ni Serengeti"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YA"," userResponse":" YA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549087867553","data":{"timestamp":" 1549087867552"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190202_090802"," gameId":" 85218cb8-aca4-4daa-b15d-aa44a66d5f35"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ya kwanza ni Serengeti"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWANZA"," userResponse":" KWANZA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549087867873","data":{"timestamp":" 1549087867872"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190202_090802"," gameId":" 85218cb8-aca4-4daa-b15d-aa44a66d5f35"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ya kwanza ni Serengeti"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NI"," userResponse":" NI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549087869128","data":{"timestamp":" 1549087869127"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190202_090802"," gameId":" 85218cb8-aca4-4daa-b15d-aa44a66d5f35"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ya kwanza ni Serengeti"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SERENGETI"," userResponse":" SERENGETI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549087872662","data":{"timestamp":" 1549087872662"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190202_090802"," gameId":" 85218cb8-aca4-4daa-b15d-aa44a66d5f35"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ngorongoro Manyara na Mikumi"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NGORONGORO"," userResponse":" NGORONGORO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549087873661","data":{"timestamp":" 1549087873660"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190202_090802"," gameId":" 85218cb8-aca4-4daa-b15d-aa44a66d5f35"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ngorongoro Manyara na Mikumi"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MANYARA"," userResponse":" MANYARA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549087873934","data":{"timestamp":" 1549087873930"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190202_090802"," gameId":" 85218cb8-aca4-4daa-b15d-aa44a66d5f35"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ngorongoro Manyara na Mikumi"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549087874884","data":{"timestamp":" 1549087874884"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190202_090802"," gameId":" 85218cb8-aca4-4daa-b15d-aa44a66d5f35"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ngorongoro Manyara na Mikumi"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MIKUMI"," userResponse":" MIKUMI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549087877774","data":{"timestamp":" 1549087877773"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190202_090802"," gameId":" 85218cb8-aca4-4daa-b15d-aa44a66d5f35"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" O Tanzania oyee!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" O"," userResponse":" O"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549087878808","data":{"timestamp":" 1549087878807"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190202_090802"," gameId":" 85218cb8-aca4-4daa-b15d-aa44a66d5f35"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" O Tanzania oyee!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TANZANIA"," userResponse":" TANZANIA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549087879289","data":{"timestamp":" 1549087879288"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190202_090802"," gameId":" 85218cb8-aca4-4daa-b15d-aa44a66d5f35"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" O Tanzania oyee!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" OYEE"," userResponse":" OYEE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549087883863","data":{"timestamp":" 1549087883862"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190202_090802"," gameId":" 85218cb8-aca4-4daa-b15d-aa44a66d5f35"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" songs"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" O Tanzania oyee!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"activity_selector","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549087884022","data":{"timestamp":" 1549087884022"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190202_090802"," gameId":" 85218cb8-aca4-4daa-b15d-aa44a66d5f35"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" O Tanzania oyee!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" OYEE"," userResponse":" OYEE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:ja..ja.syl.rand.all.stat.show.23","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549087893794","data":{"timestamp":" 1549087893794"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190202_090802"," gameId":" 883890ff-88f8-4596-a7f1-2f83b4ee3d6a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_ja..ja.syl.rand.all.stat.show.23"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_ja_ja-mpe-vyu"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" ja"," userResponse":" ja"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:ja..ja.syl.rand.all.stat.show.23","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549087898775","data":{"timestamp":" 1549087898775"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190202_090802"," gameId":" 883890ff-88f8-4596-a7f1-2f83b4ee3d6a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_ja..ja.syl.rand.all.stat.show.23"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_ja_ng'i-ng'e-ja"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" ja"," userResponse":" ja"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:ja..ja.syl.rand.all.stat.show.23","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549087903527","data":{"timestamp":" 1549087903527"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190202_090802"," gameId":" 883890ff-88f8-4596-a7f1-2f83b4ee3d6a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_ja..ja.syl.rand.all.stat.show.23"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_ja_ja-te-ti"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" ja"," userResponse":" ja"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:ja..ja.syl.rand.all.stat.show.23","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549087909476","data":{"timestamp":" 1549087909476"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190202_090802"," gameId":" 883890ff-88f8-4596-a7f1-2f83b4ee3d6a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_ja..ja.syl.rand.all.stat.show.23"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_ja_pi-ki-ja"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" ja"," userResponse":" ja"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:ja..ja.syl.rand.all.stat.show.23","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549087913676","data":{"timestamp":" 1549087913676"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190202_090802"," gameId":" 883890ff-88f8-4596-a7f1-2f83b4ee3d6a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_ja..ja.syl.rand.all.stat.show.23"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_ja_ja-ri-mmo"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" ja"," userResponse":" ja"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:ja..ja.syl.rand.all.stat.show.23","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549087918265","data":{"timestamp":" 1549087918265"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190202_090802"," gameId":" 883890ff-88f8-4596-a7f1-2f83b4ee3d6a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_ja..ja.syl.rand.all.stat.show.23"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_ja_mno-ja-ta"," problemNumber":" 6"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" ja"," userResponse":" ja"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:ja..ja.syl.rand.all.stat.show.23","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549087923099","data":{"timestamp":" 1549087923099"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190202_090802"," gameId":" 883890ff-88f8-4596-a7f1-2f83b4ee3d6a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_ja..ja.syl.rand.all.stat.show.23"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_ja_twa-chu-ja"," problemNumber":" 7"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" ja"," userResponse":" ja"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:ja..ja.syl.rand.all.stat.show.23","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549087927845","data":{"timestamp":" 1549087927845"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190202_090802"," gameId":" 883890ff-88f8-4596-a7f1-2f83b4ee3d6a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_ja..ja.syl.rand.all.stat.show.23"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_ja_vi-ja-mpi"," problemNumber":" 8"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" ja"," userResponse":" ja"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:ja..ja.syl.rand.all.stat.show.23","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549087932644","data":{"timestamp":" 1549087932644"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190202_090802"," gameId":" 883890ff-88f8-4596-a7f1-2f83b4ee3d6a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_ja..ja.syl.rand.all.stat.show.23"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_ja_we-ja-ng'i"," problemNumber":" 9"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" ja"," userResponse":" ja"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:ja..ja.syl.rand.all.stat.show.23","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549087937410","data":{"timestamp":" 1549087937410"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190202_090802"," gameId":" 883890ff-88f8-4596-a7f1-2f83b4ee3d6a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_ja..ja.syl.rand.all.stat.show.23"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_ja_po-nyi-ja"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" ja"," userResponse":" ja"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:ja..ja.syl.rand.all.stat.show.23","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549087943158","data":{"timestamp":" 1549087943157"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190202_090802"," gameId":" 883890ff-88f8-4596-a7f1-2f83b4ee3d6a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_ja..ja.syl.rand.all.stat.show.23"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" BPOP_ja_po-nyi-ja"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.mn:0..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF1-BL4.incr.1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549087953221","data":{"timestamp":" 1549087953221"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190202_090802"," gameId":" f9fa9402-d54f-4671-b5f2-2c4d38244121"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.mn_0..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF1-BL4.incr.1"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_10_2-10-11"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 10"," userResponse":" 10"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.mn:0..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF1-BL4.incr.1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549087962063","data":{"timestamp":" 1549087962063"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190202_090802"," gameId":" f9fa9402-d54f-4671-b5f2-2c4d38244121"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.mn_0..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF1-BL4.incr.1"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_7_10-3-7"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 7"," userResponse":" 7"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.mn:0..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF1-BL4.incr.1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549087966421","data":{"timestamp":" 1549087966421"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190202_090802"," gameId":" f9fa9402-d54f-4671-b5f2-2c4d38244121"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.mn_0..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF1-BL4.incr.1"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_9_0-9-7"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 9"," userResponse":" 9"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.mn:0..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF1-BL4.incr.1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549087972014","data":{"timestamp":" 1549087972014"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190202_090802"," gameId":" f9fa9402-d54f-4671-b5f2-2c4d38244121"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.mn_0..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF1-BL4.incr.1"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_12_12-5-6"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 12"," userResponse":" 12"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.mn:0..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF1-BL4.incr.1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549087977854","data":{"timestamp":" 1549087977854"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190202_090802"," gameId":" f9fa9402-d54f-4671-b5f2-2c4d38244121"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.mn_0..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF1-BL4.incr.1"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_11_10-11-12"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 11"," userResponse":" 11"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.mn:0..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF1-BL4.incr.1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549087983025","data":{"timestamp":" 1549087983025"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190202_090802"," gameId":" f9fa9402-d54f-4671-b5f2-2c4d38244121"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.mn_0..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF1-BL4.incr.1"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_12_13-12-5"," problemNumber":" 6"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 12"," userResponse":" 12"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.mn:0..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF1-BL4.incr.1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549087988121","data":{"timestamp":" 1549087988121"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190202_090802"," gameId":" f9fa9402-d54f-4671-b5f2-2c4d38244121"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.mn_0..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF1-BL4.incr.1"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_10_1-10-6"," problemNumber":" 7"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 10"," userResponse":" 10"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.mn:0..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF1-BL4.incr.1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549087992649","data":{"timestamp":" 1549087992649"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190202_090802"," gameId":" f9fa9402-d54f-4671-b5f2-2c4d38244121"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.mn_0..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF1-BL4.incr.1"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_3_3-13-6"," problemNumber":" 8"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 3"," userResponse":" 3"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.mn:0..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF1-BL4.incr.1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549087998893","data":{"timestamp":" 1549087998893"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190202_090802"," gameId":" f9fa9402-d54f-4671-b5f2-2c4d38244121"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.mn_0..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF1-BL4.incr.1"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_4_0-4-13"," problemNumber":" 9"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 4"," userResponse":" 4"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.mn:0..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF1-BL4.incr.1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549088004727","data":{"timestamp":" 1549088004727"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190202_090802"," gameId":" f9fa9402-d54f-4671-b5f2-2c4d38244121"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.mn_0..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF1-BL4.incr.1"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_10_3-10-2"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 10"," userResponse":" 10"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.mn:0..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF1-BL4.incr.1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549088011249","data":{"timestamp":" 1549088011248"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190202_090802"," gameId":" f9fa9402-d54f-4671-b5f2-2c4d38244121"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.mn_0..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF1-BL4.incr.1"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" BPOP_10_3-10-2"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::syl.ja..ju.asc.lc.8","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549088022945","data":{"timestamp":" 1549088022945"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190202_090802"," gameId":" 2f794663-7755-427e-8027-0b3bf8ec92ee"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__syl.ja..ju.asc.lc.8"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" ja"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" JA"," userResponse":" JA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::syl.ja..ju.asc.lc.8","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549088027905","data":{"timestamp":" 1549088027905"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190202_090802"," gameId":" 2f794663-7755-427e-8027-0b3bf8ec92ee"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__syl.ja..ju.asc.lc.8"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" ja"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" JA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::syl.ja..ju.asc.lc.8","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549088029487","data":{"timestamp":" 1549088029487"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190202_090802"," gameId":" 2f794663-7755-427e-8027-0b3bf8ec92ee"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__syl.ja..ju.asc.lc.8"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" je"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" JE"," userResponse":" JE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::syl.ja..ju.asc.lc.8","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549088036590","data":{"timestamp":" 1549088036590"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190202_090802"," gameId":" 2f794663-7755-427e-8027-0b3bf8ec92ee"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__syl.ja..ju.asc.lc.8"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" je"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" JE"," userResponse":" JE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::syl.ja..ju.asc.lc.8","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549088038200","data":{"timestamp":" 1549088038200"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190202_090802"," gameId":" 2f794663-7755-427e-8027-0b3bf8ec92ee"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__syl.ja..ju.asc.lc.8"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" ji"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" JI"," userResponse":" JI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::syl.ja..ju.asc.lc.8","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549088040315","data":{"timestamp":" 1549088040315"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190202_090802"," gameId":" 2f794663-7755-427e-8027-0b3bf8ec92ee"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__syl.ja..ju.asc.lc.8"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" ji"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" JI"," userResponse":" JI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::syl.ja..ju.asc.lc.8","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549088041943","data":{"timestamp":" 1549088041942"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190202_090802"," gameId":" 2f794663-7755-427e-8027-0b3bf8ec92ee"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__syl.ja..ju.asc.lc.8"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" jo"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" JO"," userResponse":" JO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::syl.ja..ju.asc.lc.8","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549088043974","data":{"timestamp":" 1549088043974"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190202_090802"," gameId":" 2f794663-7755-427e-8027-0b3bf8ec92ee"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__syl.ja..ju.asc.lc.8"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" jo"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" JO"," userResponse":" JO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::syl.ja..ju.asc.lc.8","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549088045560","data":{"timestamp":" 1549088045560"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190202_090802"," gameId":" 2f794663-7755-427e-8027-0b3bf8ec92ee"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__syl.ja..ju.asc.lc.8"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" ju"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" JU"," userResponse":" JU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::syl.ja..ju.asc.lc.8","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549088047570","data":{"timestamp":" 1549088047570"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190202_090802"," gameId":" 2f794663-7755-427e-8027-0b3bf8ec92ee"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__syl.ja..ju.asc.lc.8"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" ju"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" JU"," userResponse":" JU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::syl.ja..ju.asc.lc.8","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549088049591","data":{"timestamp":" 1549088049590"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190202_090802"," gameId":" 2f794663-7755-427e-8027-0b3bf8ec92ee"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__syl.ja..ju.asc.lc.8"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" ju"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"activity_selector","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549088049694","data":{"timestamp":" 1549088049694"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190202_090802"," gameId":" 2f794663-7755-427e-8027-0b3bf8ec92ee"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__syl.ja..ju.asc.lc.8"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" ju"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" JU"," userResponse":" JU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549088057134","data":{"timestamp":" 1549088057134"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190202_090802"," gameId":" 2f794663-7755-427e-8027-0b3bf8ec92ee"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__syl.ja..ju.asc.lc.8"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" ju"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::syl.ja..ju.asc.lc.23","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549088064226","data":{"timestamp":" 1549088064226"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190202_090802"," gameId":" 2f794663-7755-427e-8027-0b3bf8ec92ee"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__syl.ja..ju.asc.lc.8"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" ju"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.mn:0..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF1-BL3.incr.2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549088074577","data":{"timestamp":" 1549088074577"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190202_090802"," gameId":" be771d23-88aa-4673-bbe8-6715c33eb782"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.mn_0..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF1-BL3.incr.2"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_3_3-5-6"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 3"," userResponse":" 3"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.mn:0..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF1-BL3.incr.2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549088079532","data":{"timestamp":" 1549088079532"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190202_090802"," gameId":" be771d23-88aa-4673-bbe8-6715c33eb782"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.mn_0..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF1-BL3.incr.2"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_10_10-2-4"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 10"," userResponse":" 10"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.mn:0..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF1-BL3.incr.2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549088084847","data":{"timestamp":" 1549088084847"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190202_090802"," gameId":" be771d23-88aa-4673-bbe8-6715c33eb782"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.mn_0..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF1-BL3.incr.2"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_7_2-11-7"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 7"," userResponse":" 7"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.mn:0..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF1-BL3.incr.2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549088089221","data":{"timestamp":" 1549088089221"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190202_090802"," gameId":" be771d23-88aa-4673-bbe8-6715c33eb782"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.mn_0..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF1-BL3.incr.2"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_7_3-4-7"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 7"," userResponse":" 7"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.mn:0..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF1-BL3.incr.2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549088093558","data":{"timestamp":" 1549088093558"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190202_090802"," gameId":" be771d23-88aa-4673-bbe8-6715c33eb782"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.mn_0..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF1-BL3.incr.2"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_7_11-13-7"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 7"," userResponse":" 7"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.mn:0..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF1-BL3.incr.2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549088102439","data":{"timestamp":" 1549088102439"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190202_090802"," gameId":" be771d23-88aa-4673-bbe8-6715c33eb782"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.mn_0..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF1-BL3.incr.2"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_5_2-12-5"," problemNumber":" 6"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 5"," userResponse":" 5"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.mn:0..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF1-BL3.incr.2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549088107628","data":{"timestamp":" 1549088107627"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190202_090802"," gameId":" be771d23-88aa-4673-bbe8-6715c33eb782"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.mn_0..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF1-BL3.incr.2"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_10_8-10-7"," problemNumber":" 7"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 10"," userResponse":" 10"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.mn:0..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF1-BL3.incr.2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549088112212","data":{"timestamp":" 1549088112212"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190202_090802"," gameId":" be771d23-88aa-4673-bbe8-6715c33eb782"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.mn_0..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF1-BL3.incr.2"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_3_8-3-5"," problemNumber":" 8"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 3"," userResponse":" 3"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.mn:0..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF1-BL3.incr.2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549088118059","data":{"timestamp":" 1549088118059"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190202_090802"," gameId":" be771d23-88aa-4673-bbe8-6715c33eb782"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.mn_0..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF1-BL3.incr.2"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_9_9-2-7"," problemNumber":" 9"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 9"," userResponse":" 9"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.mn:0..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF1-BL3.incr.2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549088122552","data":{"timestamp":" 1549088122552"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190202_090802"," gameId":" be771d23-88aa-4673-bbe8-6715c33eb782"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.mn_0..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF1-BL3.incr.2"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_10_8-10-5"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 10"," userResponse":" 10"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.mn:0..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF1-BL3.incr.2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549088129076","data":{"timestamp":" 1549088129074"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190202_090802"," gameId":" be771d23-88aa-4673-bbe8-6715c33eb782"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.mn_0..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF1-BL3.incr.2"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" BPOP_10_8-10-5"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:2ch..2ch.syl.rand.sim.stat.show.48__it_8","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549088137809","data":{"timestamp":" 1549088137809"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190202_090802"," gameId":" c40bf2d7-3d67-4cfc-984b-2213464dbacf"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_2ch..2ch.syl.rand.sim.stat.show.48__it_8"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_ri_ri-fi-si"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" ri"," userResponse":" ri"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:2ch..2ch.syl.rand.sim.stat.show.48__it_8","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549088142309","data":{"timestamp":" 1549088142309"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190202_090802"," gameId":" c40bf2d7-3d67-4cfc-984b-2213464dbacf"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_2ch..2ch.syl.rand.sim.stat.show.48__it_8"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_vo_vo-po-to"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" vo"," userResponse":" vo"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:2ch..2ch.syl.rand.sim.stat.show.48__it_8","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549088146851","data":{"timestamp":" 1549088146851"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190202_090802"," gameId":" c40bf2d7-3d67-4cfc-984b-2213464dbacf"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_2ch..2ch.syl.rand.sim.stat.show.48__it_8"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_me_le-me-re"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" me"," userResponse":" me"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:2ch..2ch.syl.rand.sim.stat.show.48__it_8","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549088158029","data":{"timestamp":" 1549088158029"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190202_090802"," gameId":" c40bf2d7-3d67-4cfc-984b-2213464dbacf"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_2ch..2ch.syl.rand.sim.stat.show.48__it_8"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_li_li-ji-si"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" li"," userResponse":" li"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:2ch..2ch.syl.rand.sim.stat.show.48__it_8","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549088162235","data":{"timestamp":" 1549088162234"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190202_090802"," gameId":" c40bf2d7-3d67-4cfc-984b-2213464dbacf"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_2ch..2ch.syl.rand.sim.stat.show.48__it_8"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_pu_pu-ru-lu"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" pu"," userResponse":" pu"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:2ch..2ch.syl.rand.sim.stat.show.48__it_8","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549088166712","data":{"timestamp":" 1549088166712"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190202_090802"," gameId":" c40bf2d7-3d67-4cfc-984b-2213464dbacf"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_2ch..2ch.syl.rand.sim.stat.show.48__it_8"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_go_go-lo-po"," problemNumber":" 6"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" go"," userResponse":" go"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:2ch..2ch.syl.rand.sim.stat.show.48__it_8","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549088171087","data":{"timestamp":" 1549088171087"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190202_090802"," gameId":" c40bf2d7-3d67-4cfc-984b-2213464dbacf"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_2ch..2ch.syl.rand.sim.stat.show.48__it_8"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_fa_fa-ra-sa"," problemNumber":" 7"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" fa"," userResponse":" fa"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:2ch..2ch.syl.rand.sim.stat.show.48__it_8","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549088175874","data":{"timestamp":" 1549088175873"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190202_090802"," gameId":" c40bf2d7-3d67-4cfc-984b-2213464dbacf"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_2ch..2ch.syl.rand.sim.stat.show.48__it_8"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_bu_bu-zu-fu"," problemNumber":" 8"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" bu"," userResponse":" bu"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:2ch..2ch.syl.rand.sim.stat.show.48__it_8","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549088180102","data":{"timestamp":" 1549088180102"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190202_090802"," gameId":" c40bf2d7-3d67-4cfc-984b-2213464dbacf"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_2ch..2ch.syl.rand.sim.stat.show.48__it_8"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_mo_mo-ko-ro"," problemNumber":" 9"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" mo"," userResponse":" mo"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:2ch..2ch.syl.rand.sim.stat.show.48__it_8","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549088184143","data":{"timestamp":" 1549088184143"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190202_090802"," gameId":" c40bf2d7-3d67-4cfc-984b-2213464dbacf"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_2ch..2ch.syl.rand.sim.stat.show.48__it_8"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_po_po-to-vo"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" po"," userResponse":" po"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:2ch..2ch.syl.rand.sim.stat.show.48__it_8","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549088189883","data":{"timestamp":" 1549088189881"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190202_090802"," gameId":" c40bf2d7-3d67-4cfc-984b-2213464dbacf"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_2ch..2ch.syl.rand.sim.stat.show.48__it_8"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" BPOP_po_po-to-vo"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549088205406","data":{"timestamp":" 1549088205406"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190202_090802"," gameId":" 0ef3f517-6abe-4e2c-b7e2-b8be88e27bae"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mbuga za wanyama Tanzania"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MBUGA"," userResponse":" MBUGA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549088205639","data":{"timestamp":" 1549088205639"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190202_090802"," gameId":" 0ef3f517-6abe-4e2c-b7e2-b8be88e27bae"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mbuga za wanyama Tanzania"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ZA"," userResponse":" ZA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549088206617","data":{"timestamp":" 1549088206616"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190202_090802"," gameId":" 0ef3f517-6abe-4e2c-b7e2-b8be88e27bae"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mbuga za wanyama Tanzania"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WANYAMA"," userResponse":" WANYAMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549088207890","data":{"timestamp":" 1549088207890"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190202_090802"," gameId":" 0ef3f517-6abe-4e2c-b7e2-b8be88e27bae"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mbuga za wanyama Tanzania"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TANZANIA"," userResponse":" TANZANIA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549088207951","data":{"timestamp":" 1549088207951"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190202_090802"," gameId":" 0ef3f517-6abe-4e2c-b7e2-b8be88e27bae"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" songs"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" Mbuga za wanyama Tanzania"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"activity_selector","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549088208030","data":{"timestamp":" 1549088208030"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190202_090802"," gameId":" 0ef3f517-6abe-4e2c-b7e2-b8be88e27bae"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mbuga za wanyama Tanzania"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TANZANIA"," userResponse":" TANZANIA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:ku..ku.syl.rand.all.stat.show.26","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549088217410","data":{"timestamp":" 1549088217410"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190202_090802"," gameId":" 9d45cddf-6e8a-4fac-87f2-4e8e049713b1"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_ku..ku.syl.rand.all.stat.show.26"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_ku_ng'e-ku-ndu"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" ku"," userResponse":" ku"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:ku..ku.syl.rand.all.stat.show.26","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549088222145","data":{"timestamp":" 1549088222145"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190202_090802"," gameId":" 9d45cddf-6e8a-4fac-87f2-4e8e049713b1"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_ku..ku.syl.rand.all.stat.show.26"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_ku_bwe-vyo-ku"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" ku"," userResponse":" ku"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:ku..ku.syl.rand.all.stat.show.26","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549088226537","data":{"timestamp":" 1549088226537"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190202_090802"," gameId":" 9d45cddf-6e8a-4fac-87f2-4e8e049713b1"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_ku..ku.syl.rand.all.stat.show.26"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_ku_ku-nje-ya"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" ku"," userResponse":" ku"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:ku..ku.syl.rand.all.stat.show.26","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549088230904","data":{"timestamp":" 1549088230904"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190202_090802"," gameId":" 9d45cddf-6e8a-4fac-87f2-4e8e049713b1"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_ku..ku.syl.rand.all.stat.show.26"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_ku_kwa-da-ku"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" ku"," userResponse":" ku"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:ku..ku.syl.rand.all.stat.show.26","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549088235003","data":{"timestamp":" 1549088235003"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190202_090802"," gameId":" 9d45cddf-6e8a-4fac-87f2-4e8e049713b1"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_ku..ku.syl.rand.all.stat.show.26"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_ku_ku-ngi-ze"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" ku"," userResponse":" ku"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:ku..ku.syl.rand.all.stat.show.26","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549088239654","data":{"timestamp":" 1549088239654"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190202_090802"," gameId":" 9d45cddf-6e8a-4fac-87f2-4e8e049713b1"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_ku..ku.syl.rand.all.stat.show.26"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_ku_ka-ku-mwe"," problemNumber":" 6"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" ku"," userResponse":" ku"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:ku..ku.syl.rand.all.stat.show.26","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549088244098","data":{"timestamp":" 1549088244097"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190202_090802"," gameId":" 9d45cddf-6e8a-4fac-87f2-4e8e049713b1"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_ku..ku.syl.rand.all.stat.show.26"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_ku_mvu-ku-ka"," problemNumber":" 7"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" ku"," userResponse":" ku"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:ku..ku.syl.rand.all.stat.show.26","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549088248902","data":{"timestamp":" 1549088248902"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190202_090802"," gameId":" 9d45cddf-6e8a-4fac-87f2-4e8e049713b1"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_ku..ku.syl.rand.all.stat.show.26"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_ku_ndi-mli-ku"," problemNumber":" 8"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" ku"," userResponse":" ku"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:ku..ku.syl.rand.all.stat.show.26","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549088253458","data":{"timestamp":" 1549088253458"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190202_090802"," gameId":" 9d45cddf-6e8a-4fac-87f2-4e8e049713b1"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_ku..ku.syl.rand.all.stat.show.26"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_ku_ku-ya-nye"," problemNumber":" 9"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" ku"," userResponse":" ku"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:ku..ku.syl.rand.all.stat.show.26","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549088257996","data":{"timestamp":" 1549088257996"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190202_090802"," gameId":" 9d45cddf-6e8a-4fac-87f2-4e8e049713b1"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_ku..ku.syl.rand.all.stat.show.26"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_ku_ku-do-njo"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" ku"," userResponse":" ku"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:ku..ku.syl.rand.all.stat.show.26","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549088263759","data":{"timestamp":" 1549088263755"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190202_090802"," gameId":" 9d45cddf-6e8a-4fac-87f2-4e8e049713b1"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_ku..ku.syl.rand.all.stat.show.26"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" BPOP_ku_ku-do-njo"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"num.scale:2..12.off1.2__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549088276386","data":{"timestamp":" 1549088276386"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190202_090802"," gameId":" 9d45cddf-6e8a-4fac-87f2-4e8e049713b1"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_ku..ku.syl.rand.all.stat.show.26"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" BPOP_ku_ku-do-njo"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::syl.ka..ku.asc.lc.9","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549088286234","data":{"timestamp":" 1549088286233"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190202_090802"," gameId":" dabf0a74-c48e-41fd-8755-f384b0ab5bd5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__syl.ka..ku.asc.lc.9"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" ka"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KA"," userResponse":" KA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::syl.ka..ku.asc.lc.9","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549088288872","data":{"timestamp":" 1549088288872"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190202_090802"," gameId":" dabf0a74-c48e-41fd-8755-f384b0ab5bd5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__syl.ka..ku.asc.lc.9"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" ka"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::syl.ka..ku.asc.lc.9","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549088290425","data":{"timestamp":" 1549088290425"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190202_090802"," gameId":" dabf0a74-c48e-41fd-8755-f384b0ab5bd5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__syl.ka..ku.asc.lc.9"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" ki"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KI"," userResponse":" KI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::syl.ka..ku.asc.lc.9","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549088302258","data":{"timestamp":" 1549088302258"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190202_090802"," gameId":" dabf0a74-c48e-41fd-8755-f384b0ab5bd5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__syl.ka..ku.asc.lc.9"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" ki"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"activity_selector","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549088302515","data":{"timestamp":" 1549088302515"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190202_090802"," gameId":" dabf0a74-c48e-41fd-8755-f384b0ab5bd5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__syl.ka..ku.asc.lc.9"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" ki"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KI"," userResponse":" KI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::syl.ka..ku.asc.lc.9","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549088314049","data":{"timestamp":" 1549088314048"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190202_090802"," gameId":" bfa55fab-e492-472b-9b48-5572fc3a74bc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__syl.ka..ku.asc.lc.9"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" ka"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KA"," userResponse":" KA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::syl.ka..ku.asc.lc.9","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549088316091","data":{"timestamp":" 1549088316091"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190202_090802"," gameId":" bfa55fab-e492-472b-9b48-5572fc3a74bc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__syl.ka..ku.asc.lc.9"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" ka"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KA"," userResponse":" KA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::syl.ka..ku.asc.lc.9","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549088317693","data":{"timestamp":" 1549088317693"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190202_090802"," gameId":" bfa55fab-e492-472b-9b48-5572fc3a74bc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__syl.ka..ku.asc.lc.9"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" ke"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KE"," userResponse":" KE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::syl.ka..ku.asc.lc.9","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549088319976","data":{"timestamp":" 1549088319976"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190202_090802"," gameId":" bfa55fab-e492-472b-9b48-5572fc3a74bc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__syl.ka..ku.asc.lc.9"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" ke"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KE"," userResponse":" KE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::syl.ka..ku.asc.lc.9","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549088321579","data":{"timestamp":" 1549088321579"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190202_090802"," gameId":" bfa55fab-e492-472b-9b48-5572fc3a74bc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__syl.ka..ku.asc.lc.9"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" ki"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KI"," userResponse":" KI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::syl.ka..ku.asc.lc.9","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549088324897","data":{"timestamp":" 1549088324897"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190202_090802"," gameId":" bfa55fab-e492-472b-9b48-5572fc3a74bc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__syl.ka..ku.asc.lc.9"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" ki"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KI"," userResponse":" KI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::syl.ka..ku.asc.lc.9","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549088326485","data":{"timestamp":" 1549088326485"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190202_090802"," gameId":" bfa55fab-e492-472b-9b48-5572fc3a74bc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__syl.ka..ku.asc.lc.9"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" ko"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KO"," userResponse":" KO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::syl.ka..ku.asc.lc.9","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549088329649","data":{"timestamp":" 1549088329649"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190202_090802"," gameId":" bfa55fab-e492-472b-9b48-5572fc3a74bc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__syl.ka..ku.asc.lc.9"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" ko"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KO"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::syl.ka..ku.asc.lc.9","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549088331207","data":{"timestamp":" 1549088331207"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190202_090802"," gameId":" bfa55fab-e492-472b-9b48-5572fc3a74bc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__syl.ka..ku.asc.lc.9"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" ku"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KU"," userResponse":" KU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::syl.ka..ku.asc.lc.9","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549088334079","data":{"timestamp":" 1549088334079"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190202_090802"," gameId":" bfa55fab-e492-472b-9b48-5572fc3a74bc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__syl.ka..ku.asc.lc.9"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" ku"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KU"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::syl.ka..ku.asc.lc.9","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549088336093","data":{"timestamp":" 1549088336093"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190202_090802"," gameId":" bfa55fab-e492-472b-9b48-5572fc3a74bc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__syl.ka..ku.asc.lc.9"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" ku"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"activity_selector","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549088336260","data":{"timestamp":" 1549088336259"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190202_090802"," gameId":" bfa55fab-e492-472b-9b48-5572fc3a74bc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__syl.ka..ku.asc.lc.9"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" ku"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KU"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549088341918","data":{"timestamp":" 1549088341918"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190202_090802"," gameId":" bfa55fab-e492-472b-9b48-5572fc3a74bc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__syl.ka..ku.asc.lc.9"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" ku"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:ku..ku.syl.rand.all.stat.noShow.28","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549088351384","data":{"timestamp":" 1549088351384"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190202_090802"," gameId":" 4818655a-c8dd-4f5f-8b88-5d1f269e58c8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_ku..ku.syl.rand.all.stat.noShow.28"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_ku_ku-na-gi"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" ku"," userResponse":" ku"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:ku..ku.syl.rand.all.stat.noShow.28","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549088352170","data":{"timestamp":" 1549088352170"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190202_090802"," gameId":" 4818655a-c8dd-4f5f-8b88-5d1f269e58c8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_ku..ku.syl.rand.all.stat.noShow.28"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" BPOP_ku_ku-na-gi"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.mn:0..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF1-BL3.incr.2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549088361927","data":{"timestamp":" 1549088361927"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190202_090802"," gameId":" 1c24e1bf-a2d8-4fe8-9e79-22bfe5d9e29c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.mn_0..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF1-BL3.incr.2"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_5_2-12-5"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 5"," userResponse":" 5"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.mn:0..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF1-BL3.incr.2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549088366233","data":{"timestamp":" 1549088366233"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190202_090802"," gameId":" 1c24e1bf-a2d8-4fe8-9e79-22bfe5d9e29c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.mn_0..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF1-BL3.incr.2"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_10_8-10-7"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 10"," userResponse":" 10"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.mn:0..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF1-BL3.incr.2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549088370429","data":{"timestamp":" 1549088370429"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190202_090802"," gameId":" 1c24e1bf-a2d8-4fe8-9e79-22bfe5d9e29c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.mn_0..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF1-BL3.incr.2"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_10_10-2-4"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 10"," userResponse":" 4"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.mn:0..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF1-BL3.incr.2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549088376541","data":{"timestamp":" 1549088376541"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190202_090802"," gameId":" 1c24e1bf-a2d8-4fe8-9e79-22bfe5d9e29c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.mn_0..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF1-BL3.incr.2"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_10_10-2-4"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 10"," userResponse":" 10"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.mn:0..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF1-BL3.incr.2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549088380873","data":{"timestamp":" 1549088380873"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190202_090802"," gameId":" 1c24e1bf-a2d8-4fe8-9e79-22bfe5d9e29c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.mn_0..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF1-BL3.incr.2"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_7_3-4-7"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 7"," userResponse":" 4"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.mn:0..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF1-BL3.incr.2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549088387569","data":{"timestamp":" 1549088387569"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190202_090802"," gameId":" 1c24e1bf-a2d8-4fe8-9e79-22bfe5d9e29c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.mn_0..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF1-BL3.incr.2"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_7_3-4-7"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 7"," userResponse":" 7"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.mn:0..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF1-BL3.incr.2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549088393685","data":{"timestamp":" 1549088393685"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190202_090802"," gameId":" 1c24e1bf-a2d8-4fe8-9e79-22bfe5d9e29c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.mn_0..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF1-BL3.incr.2"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_3_3-5-6"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 3"," userResponse":" 3"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.mn:0..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF1-BL3.incr.2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549088399185","data":{"timestamp":" 1549088399185"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190202_090802"," gameId":" 1c24e1bf-a2d8-4fe8-9e79-22bfe5d9e29c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.mn_0..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF1-BL3.incr.2"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_9_9-2-7"," problemNumber":" 6"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 9"," userResponse":" 9"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.mn:0..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF1-BL3.incr.2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549088404161","data":{"timestamp":" 1549088404161"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190202_090802"," gameId":" 1c24e1bf-a2d8-4fe8-9e79-22bfe5d9e29c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.mn_0..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF1-BL3.incr.2"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_7_11-13-7"," problemNumber":" 7"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 7"," userResponse":" 7"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.mn:0..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF1-BL3.incr.2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549088408597","data":{"timestamp":" 1549088408596"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190202_090802"," gameId":" 1c24e1bf-a2d8-4fe8-9e79-22bfe5d9e29c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.mn_0..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF1-BL3.incr.2"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_3_8-3-5"," problemNumber":" 8"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 3"," userResponse":" 3"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.mn:0..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF1-BL3.incr.2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549088412748","data":{"timestamp":" 1549088412748"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190202_090802"," gameId":" 1c24e1bf-a2d8-4fe8-9e79-22bfe5d9e29c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.mn_0..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF1-BL3.incr.2"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_10_8-10-5"," problemNumber":" 9"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 10"," userResponse":" 10"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.mn:0..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF1-BL3.incr.2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549088416687","data":{"timestamp":" 1549088416687"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190202_090802"," gameId":" 1c24e1bf-a2d8-4fe8-9e79-22bfe5d9e29c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.mn_0..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF1-BL3.incr.2"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_7_2-11-7"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 7"," userResponse":" 7"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.mn:0..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF1-BL3.incr.2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549088423358","data":{"timestamp":" 1549088423358"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190202_090802"," gameId":" 1c24e1bf-a2d8-4fe8-9e79-22bfe5d9e29c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.mn_0..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF1-BL3.incr.2"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" BPOP_7_2-11-7"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:2ch..2ch.syl.rand.all.stat.show.47__it_9","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549088432691","data":{"timestamp":" 1549088432691"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190202_090802"," gameId":" 7dbfde82-f8b9-4253-91b7-89e14af0aef1"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_2ch..2ch.syl.rand.all.stat.show.47__it_9"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_po_po-no-da"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" po"," userResponse":" po"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:2ch..2ch.syl.rand.all.stat.show.47__it_9","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549088434241","data":{"timestamp":" 1549088434240"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190202_090802"," gameId":" 7dbfde82-f8b9-4253-91b7-89e14af0aef1"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_2ch..2ch.syl.rand.all.stat.show.47__it_9"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" BPOP_po_po-no-da"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549088439207","data":{"timestamp":" 1549088439207"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190202_090802"," gameId":" 7dbfde82-f8b9-4253-91b7-89e14af0aef1"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_2ch..2ch.syl.rand.all.stat.show.47__it_9"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" BPOP_po_po-no-da"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::syl.ka..ku.asc.lc.24","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549088446433","data":{"timestamp":" 1549088446432"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190202_090802"," gameId":" 7dbfde82-f8b9-4253-91b7-89e14af0aef1"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_2ch..2ch.syl.rand.all.stat.show.47__it_9"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" BPOP_po_po-no-da"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"num.scale:2..12.off1.2__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549088452873","data":{"timestamp":" 1549088452873"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190202_090802"," gameId":" 7dbfde82-f8b9-4253-91b7-89e14af0aef1"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_2ch..2ch.syl.rand.all.stat.show.47__it_9"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" BPOP_po_po-no-da"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:2ch..2ch.syl.rand.sim.stat.show.48__it_9","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549088461471","data":{"timestamp":" 1549088461471"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190202_090802"," gameId":" 19932b81-842e-4c48-ad6b-b8da65ef3007"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_2ch..2ch.syl.rand.sim.stat.show.48__it_9"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_po_po-to-vo"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" po"," userResponse":" po"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:2ch..2ch.syl.rand.sim.stat.show.48__it_9","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549088465353","data":{"timestamp":" 1549088465352"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190202_090802"," gameId":" 19932b81-842e-4c48-ad6b-b8da65ef3007"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_2ch..2ch.syl.rand.sim.stat.show.48__it_9"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" BPOP_po_po-to-vo"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549088469861","data":{"timestamp":" 1549088469860"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190202_090802"," gameId":" 19932b81-842e-4c48-ad6b-b8da65ef3007"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_2ch..2ch.syl.rand.sim.stat.show.48__it_9"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" BPOP_po_po-to-vo"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:le..le.syl.rand.all.stat.show.29","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549088480109","data":{"timestamp":" 1549088480109"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190202_090802"," gameId":" 5b7cbe0a-2e12-485f-830d-72f756ffb737"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_le..le.syl.rand.all.stat.show.29"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_le_le-mto-swa"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" le"," userResponse":" le"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:le..le.syl.rand.all.stat.show.29","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549088484648","data":{"timestamp":" 1549088484647"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190202_090802"," gameId":" 5b7cbe0a-2e12-485f-830d-72f756ffb737"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_le..le.syl.rand.all.stat.show.29"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_le_mji-le-bwa"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" le"," userResponse":" le"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:le..le.syl.rand.all.stat.show.29","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549088488890","data":{"timestamp":" 1549088488890"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190202_090802"," gameId":" 5b7cbe0a-2e12-485f-830d-72f756ffb737"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_le..le.syl.rand.all.stat.show.29"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_le_le-mpa-ba"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" le"," userResponse":" le"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:le..le.syl.rand.all.stat.show.29","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549088493242","data":{"timestamp":" 1549088493241"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190202_090802"," gameId":" 5b7cbe0a-2e12-485f-830d-72f756ffb737"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_le..le.syl.rand.all.stat.show.29"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_le_ku-le-swa"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" le"," userResponse":" le"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:le..le.syl.rand.all.stat.show.29","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549088498920","data":{"timestamp":" 1549088498920"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190202_090802"," gameId":" 5b7cbe0a-2e12-485f-830d-72f756ffb737"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_le..le.syl.rand.all.stat.show.29"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_le_le-mwa-chu"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" le"," userResponse":" le"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:le..le.syl.rand.all.stat.show.29","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549088503679","data":{"timestamp":" 1549088503679"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190202_090802"," gameId":" 5b7cbe0a-2e12-485f-830d-72f756ffb737"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_le..le.syl.rand.all.stat.show.29"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_le_ndu-le-twa"," problemNumber":" 6"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" le"," userResponse":" le"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:le..le.syl.rand.all.stat.show.29","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549088508903","data":{"timestamp":" 1549088508903"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190202_090802"," gameId":" 5b7cbe0a-2e12-485f-830d-72f756ffb737"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_le..le.syl.rand.all.stat.show.29"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_le_si-fi-le"," problemNumber":" 7"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" le"," userResponse":" le"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:le..le.syl.rand.all.stat.show.29","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549088513555","data":{"timestamp":" 1549088513554"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190202_090802"," gameId":" 5b7cbe0a-2e12-485f-830d-72f756ffb737"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_le..le.syl.rand.all.stat.show.29"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_le_le-gha-za"," problemNumber":" 8"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" le"," userResponse":" le"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:le..le.syl.rand.all.stat.show.29","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549088518717","data":{"timestamp":" 1549088518716"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190202_090802"," gameId":" 5b7cbe0a-2e12-485f-830d-72f756ffb737"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_le..le.syl.rand.all.stat.show.29"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_le_nchi-jo-le"," problemNumber":" 9"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" le"," userResponse":" le"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:le..le.syl.rand.all.stat.show.29","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549088524609","data":{"timestamp":" 1549088524609"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190202_090802"," gameId":" 5b7cbe0a-2e12-485f-830d-72f756ffb737"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_le..le.syl.rand.all.stat.show.29"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_le_vya-le-dha"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" le"," userResponse":" le"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:le..le.syl.rand.all.stat.show.29","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549088530366","data":{"timestamp":" 1549088530366"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190202_090802"," gameId":" 5b7cbe0a-2e12-485f-830d-72f756ffb737"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_le..le.syl.rand.all.stat.show.29"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" BPOP_le_vya-le-dha"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:le..le.syl.rand.all.stat.show.29","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549088543108","data":{"timestamp":" 1549088543108"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190202_090802"," gameId":" 6acf25ab-272c-4fb1-b154-0f71b6e7aaca"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_le..le.syl.rand.all.stat.show.29"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_le_mji-le-bwa"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" le"," userResponse":" le"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:le..le.syl.rand.all.stat.show.29","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549088547962","data":{"timestamp":" 1549088547962"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190202_090802"," gameId":" 6acf25ab-272c-4fb1-b154-0f71b6e7aaca"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_le..le.syl.rand.all.stat.show.29"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_le_le-mpa-ba"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" le"," userResponse":" le"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:le..le.syl.rand.all.stat.show.29","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549088552309","data":{"timestamp":" 1549088552309"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190202_090802"," gameId":" 6acf25ab-272c-4fb1-b154-0f71b6e7aaca"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_le..le.syl.rand.all.stat.show.29"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_le_nchi-jo-le"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" le"," userResponse":" le"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:le..le.syl.rand.all.stat.show.29","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549088556769","data":{"timestamp":" 1549088556769"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190202_090802"," gameId":" 6acf25ab-272c-4fb1-b154-0f71b6e7aaca"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_le..le.syl.rand.all.stat.show.29"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_le_ndu-le-twa"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" le"," userResponse":" le"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:le..le.syl.rand.all.stat.show.29","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549088561581","data":{"timestamp":" 1549088561581"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190202_090802"," gameId":" 6acf25ab-272c-4fb1-b154-0f71b6e7aaca"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_le..le.syl.rand.all.stat.show.29"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_le_si-fi-le"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" le"," userResponse":" le"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:le..le.syl.rand.all.stat.show.29","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549088566420","data":{"timestamp":" 1549088566419"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190202_090802"," gameId":" 6acf25ab-272c-4fb1-b154-0f71b6e7aaca"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_le..le.syl.rand.all.stat.show.29"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_le_le-gha-za"," problemNumber":" 6"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" le"," userResponse":" le"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:le..le.syl.rand.all.stat.show.29","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549088570973","data":{"timestamp":" 1549088570973"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190202_090802"," gameId":" 6acf25ab-272c-4fb1-b154-0f71b6e7aaca"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_le..le.syl.rand.all.stat.show.29"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_le_vya-le-dha"," problemNumber":" 7"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" le"," userResponse":" le"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:le..le.syl.rand.all.stat.show.29","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549088577320","data":{"timestamp":" 1549088577320"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190202_090802"," gameId":" 6acf25ab-272c-4fb1-b154-0f71b6e7aaca"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_le..le.syl.rand.all.stat.show.29"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_le_le-mwa-chu"," problemNumber":" 8"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" le"," userResponse":" le"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:le..le.syl.rand.all.stat.show.29","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549088582087","data":{"timestamp":" 1549088582087"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190202_090802"," gameId":" 6acf25ab-272c-4fb1-b154-0f71b6e7aaca"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_le..le.syl.rand.all.stat.show.29"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_le_ku-le-swa"," problemNumber":" 9"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" le"," userResponse":" le"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:le..le.syl.rand.all.stat.show.29","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549088586369","data":{"timestamp":" 1549088586369"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190202_090802"," gameId":" 6acf25ab-272c-4fb1-b154-0f71b6e7aaca"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_le..le.syl.rand.all.stat.show.29"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_le_le-mto-swa"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" le"," userResponse":" le"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:le..le.syl.rand.all.stat.show.29","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549088592166","data":{"timestamp":" 1549088592166"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190202_090802"," gameId":" 6acf25ab-272c-4fb1-b154-0f71b6e7aaca"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_le..le.syl.rand.all.stat.show.29"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" BPOP_le_le-mto-swa"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.mn:0..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF1-BL3.incr.2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549088601741","data":{"timestamp":" 1549088601740"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190202_090802"," gameId":" 8884f76a-a6ec-4903-9ce4-a541e181d5aa"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.mn_0..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF1-BL3.incr.2"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_3_8-3-5"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 3"," userResponse":" 3"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.mn:0..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF1-BL3.incr.2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549088606293","data":{"timestamp":" 1549088606293"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190202_090802"," gameId":" 8884f76a-a6ec-4903-9ce4-a541e181d5aa"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.mn_0..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF1-BL3.incr.2"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_3_3-5-6"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 3"," userResponse":" 3"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.mn:0..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF1-BL3.incr.2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549088611089","data":{"timestamp":" 1549088611088"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190202_090802"," gameId":" 8884f76a-a6ec-4903-9ce4-a541e181d5aa"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.mn_0..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF1-BL3.incr.2"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_7_3-4-7"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 7"," userResponse":" 7"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.mn:0..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF1-BL3.incr.2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549088615368","data":{"timestamp":" 1549088615368"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190202_090802"," gameId":" 8884f76a-a6ec-4903-9ce4-a541e181d5aa"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.mn_0..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF1-BL3.incr.2"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_10_8-10-5"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 10"," userResponse":" 10"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.mn:0..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF1-BL3.incr.2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549088619901","data":{"timestamp":" 1549088619901"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190202_090802"," gameId":" 8884f76a-a6ec-4903-9ce4-a541e181d5aa"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.mn_0..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF1-BL3.incr.2"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_5_2-12-5"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 5"," userResponse":" 5"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.mn:0..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF1-BL3.incr.2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549088624559","data":{"timestamp":" 1549088624559"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190202_090802"," gameId":" 8884f76a-a6ec-4903-9ce4-a541e181d5aa"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.mn_0..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF1-BL3.incr.2"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_9_9-2-7"," problemNumber":" 6"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 9"," userResponse":" 9"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.mn:0..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF1-BL3.incr.2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549088629541","data":{"timestamp":" 1549088629541"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190202_090802"," gameId":" 8884f76a-a6ec-4903-9ce4-a541e181d5aa"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.mn_0..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF1-BL3.incr.2"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_10_10-2-4"," problemNumber":" 7"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 10"," userResponse":" 10"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.mn:0..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF1-BL3.incr.2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549088635467","data":{"timestamp":" 1549088635466"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190202_090802"," gameId":" 8884f76a-a6ec-4903-9ce4-a541e181d5aa"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.mn_0..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF1-BL3.incr.2"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_7_11-13-7"," problemNumber":" 8"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 7"," userResponse":" 7"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.mn:0..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF1-BL3.incr.2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549088641779","data":{"timestamp":" 1549088641779"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190202_090802"," gameId":" 8884f76a-a6ec-4903-9ce4-a541e181d5aa"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.mn_0..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF1-BL3.incr.2"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_10_8-10-7"," problemNumber":" 9"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 10"," userResponse":" 10"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.mn:0..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF1-BL3.incr.2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549088648733","data":{"timestamp":" 1549088648733"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190202_090802"," gameId":" 8884f76a-a6ec-4903-9ce4-a541e181d5aa"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.mn_0..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF1-BL3.incr.2"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_7_2-11-7"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 7"," userResponse":" 7"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.mn:0..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF1-BL3.incr.2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549088653662","data":{"timestamp":" 1549088653662"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190202_090802"," gameId":" 8884f76a-a6ec-4903-9ce4-a541e181d5aa"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.mn_0..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF1-BL3.incr.2"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" BPOP_7_2-11-7"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:le..le.syl.rand.all.stat.noShow.31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549088663666","data":{"timestamp":" 1549088663665"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190202_090802"," gameId":" 6fc07f9a-dc17-4ea8-aba2-7d1342c6a53b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_le..le.syl.rand.all.stat.noShow.31"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_le_ng'i-mtu-le"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" le"," userResponse":" le"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:le..le.syl.rand.all.stat.noShow.31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549088671251","data":{"timestamp":" 1549088671251"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190202_090802"," gameId":" 6fc07f9a-dc17-4ea8-aba2-7d1342c6a53b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_le..le.syl.rand.all.stat.noShow.31"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_le_le-nje-to"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" le"," userResponse":" le"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:le..le.syl.rand.all.stat.noShow.31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549088676081","data":{"timestamp":" 1549088676080"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190202_090802"," gameId":" 6fc07f9a-dc17-4ea8-aba2-7d1342c6a53b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_le..le.syl.rand.all.stat.noShow.31"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_le_mme-na-le"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" le"," userResponse":" le"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:le..le.syl.rand.all.stat.noShow.31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549088677709","data":{"timestamp":" 1549088677709"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190202_090802"," gameId":" 6fc07f9a-dc17-4ea8-aba2-7d1342c6a53b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_le..le.syl.rand.all.stat.noShow.31"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" BPOP_le_mme-na-le"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549088682330","data":{"timestamp":" 1549088682330"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190202_090802"," gameId":" 6fc07f9a-dc17-4ea8-aba2-7d1342c6a53b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_le..le.syl.rand.all.stat.noShow.31"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" BPOP_le_mme-na-le"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::syl.la..lu.asc.lc.25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549088688928","data":{"timestamp":" 1549088688927"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190202_090802"," gameId":" 6fc07f9a-dc17-4ea8-aba2-7d1342c6a53b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_le..le.syl.rand.all.stat.noShow.31"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" BPOP_le_mme-na-le"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.mn:0..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF1-BL2.incr.3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549088694723","data":{"timestamp":" 1549088694723"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190202_090802"," gameId":" 6fc07f9a-dc17-4ea8-aba2-7d1342c6a53b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_le..le.syl.rand.all.stat.noShow.31"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" BPOP_le_mme-na-le"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:2ch..2ch.syl.rand.all.stat.show.47__it_10","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549088701477","data":{"timestamp":" 1549088701477"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190202_090802"," gameId":" 6fc07f9a-dc17-4ea8-aba2-7d1342c6a53b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_le..le.syl.rand.all.stat.noShow.31"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" BPOP_le_mme-na-le"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549088705287","data":{"timestamp":" 1549088705287"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190202_090802"," gameId":" 6fc07f9a-dc17-4ea8-aba2-7d1342c6a53b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_le..le.syl.rand.all.stat.noShow.31"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" BPOP_le_mme-na-le"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::syl.la..lu.asc.lc.25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549088714406","data":{"timestamp":" 1549088714405"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190202_090802"," gameId":" 6fc07f9a-dc17-4ea8-aba2-7d1342c6a53b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_le..le.syl.rand.all.stat.noShow.31"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" BPOP_le_mme-na-le"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"num.scale:2..12.off1.2__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549088751253","data":{"timestamp":" 1549088751252"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190202_090802"," gameId":" 6fc07f9a-dc17-4ea8-aba2-7d1342c6a53b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_le..le.syl.rand.all.stat.noShow.31"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" BPOP_le_mme-na-le"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"end":"end"}]}